{
    "subject": "resource/32nd_Medical_Brigade",
    "predicate": "property/branch",
    "object": "Army",
    "human_readable": "The 32nd Medical Brigade is part of the Army.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9722043871879578,
            "question": "To which branch of the military does the 32nd Medical Brigade belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9398122429847717,
            "question": "What is the significance of the 32nd Medical Brigade within the Army structure?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8975883722305298,
            "question": "What is the role of the 32nd Medical Brigade?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8388732075691223,
            "question": "Who commands the 32nd Medical Brigade?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8368448615074158,
            "question": "How many personnel are in the 32nd Medical Brigade?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8015186786651611,
            "question": "Where is the headquarters of the 32nd Medical Brigade located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.758056640625,
            "question": "What are some examples of missions that the 32nd Medical Brigade might be involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7424155473709106,
            "question": "What is the history of the 32nd Medical Brigade?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7392791509628296,
            "question": "Does the 32nd Medical Brigade operate independently or as part of a larger unit?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7226532101631165,
            "question": "Are there any specific types of medical services provided by the 32nd Medical Brigade?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The 32nd Medical Brigade is part of the Army.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3847_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does the 32nd Medical Brigade operate independently or as part of a larger unit?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3847_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the history of the 32nd Medical Brigade?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3847_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some examples of missions that the 32nd Medical Brigade might be involved in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3847_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3847_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3847_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3847_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3847_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3847_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3847_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3847_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3847_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3847_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3847_62.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format containing the evaluation result:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that \"The 32nd Medical Brigade is part of the Army.\" The text explicitly states that \"The 32d Medical Brigade is a medical brigade in the United States Army\" (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3847/re-ranker-msmarco/50.txt) and that the 32nd Medical Brigade is part of the U.S. Army Medical Center of Excellence (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3847/re-ranker-msmarco/14.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly indicate that the 32nd Medical Brigade is a part of the U.S. Army, supporting the given statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}